let trematoda_ = [
    {question: "中華肝吸蟲", answer: "Clonorchis sinensis"},
    {question: "牛羊肝吸蟲", answer: "Fasciola hepatica"},
    {question: "衛氏肺吸蟲", answer: "Paragonimus westermani"},
    {question: "薑片蟲", answer: "Fasciolopsis buski"},
    {question: "異形異形吸蟲", answer: "Heterophyes heterophyes"},
    {question: "橫川異形吸蟲", answer: "Metagonimus yokogawai"},
    {question: "棘口吸蟲", answer: "Echinostoma spp"},
    {question: "日本住血吸蟲", answer: "Schistosoma japonicum"},
    {question: "埃及住血吸蟲", answer: "Schistosoma haematobium"},
    {question: "曼森住血吸蟲", answer: "Schistosoma mansoni"},
];
let protozoa_ = [
    {question: "間日瘧原蟲", answer: "Plasmodium vivax"},
    {question: "三日瘧原蟲", answer: "Plasmodium malariae"},
    {question: "惡性瘧原蟲", answer: "Plasmodium falciparum"},
    {question: "卵形瘧原蟲", answer: "Plasmodium ovale"},
    {question: "等胞球蟲", answer: "Isospora spp"},
    {question: "弓形蟲", answer: "Toxoplasma gondii"},
    {question: "肺胞子蟲", answer: "Pneumocystis carinii"},
    {question: "巴貝氏原蟲", answer: "Babesia spp"},
    {question: "大腸纖毛蟲", answer: "Balantidium coli"},
    {question: "唇形鞭毛蟲", answer: "Cheilomastix mesnili"},
    {question: "梨形鞭毛蟲", answer: "Giardia lamblia"},
    {question: "陰道鞭毛滴蟲", answer: "Trichomonas vaginalis"},
    {question: "口腔鞭毛滴蟲", answer: "Trichomonas tenax"},
    {question: "人五鞭毛滴蟲", answer: "Pentatrichomonas homnis"},
    {question: "杜氏利什曼原蟲", answer: "Leishmania donovani"},
    {question: "熱帶利什曼原蟲", answer: "Leishmania tropica"},
    {question: "巴西利什曼原蟲", answer: "Leishmania braziliensis"},
    {question: "布氏甘比亞錐蟲", answer: "Trypanosoma brucei gambiense"},
    {question: "布氏羅得西亞錐蟲", answer: "Trypanosoma brucei rhodesiense"},
    {question: "枯氏錐蟲", answer: "Trypanosoma cruzi"}
];
let amoeba_ = [
    {question: "痢疾阿米巴", answer: "Entamoeba histolytica"},
    {question: "福氏耐格里阿米巴", answer: "Naegleria fowleri"},
    {question: "棘阿米巴", answer: "Acanthamoeba spp"},
    {question: "巴拉目阿米巴", answer: "Balamuthia mandrilaris"},
    {question: "大腸阿米巴", answer: "Entamoeba coli"}
];
let snail_ = [
    {question: "顆粒洗螺", answer: "Thiara spp"},
    {question: "派螺", answer: "Parafossarulus spp"},
    {question: "鈴螺", answer: "Lymnaea spp"},
    {question: "黑螺", answer: "Hippeutis spp"},
    {question: "小扁卷螺", answer: "Segmentina spp"},
    {question: "臺灣釘螺", answer: "Oncomelania formosana"},
    {question: "大扁卷螺", answer: "Biomphalaria spp"}
];